托妮:迈克,我今天真开心.
Toni: Mike, I really had fun today.
迈克:我得说,到目前为止,今天对于我也是如此,
Mike: Well I must say, today has gone pretty much the same for me too.
但愿总是这么幸运.好了,你喜欢玩牌吗?
So far. Knock on wood. Alright, do you like card tricks?
托妮:我非常喜欢.
Toni: They're my favorite.
迈克:那好,挑一张牌,随便哪一张.好,好的,现在想一下那张牌.
Mike: Alright. Pick a card, any card. Ok. Alright. Now think of that card.
托妮:整张牌?
Toni: The whole card?
Mike: Yeah, the whole thing. Ok, now, was your card the ace of spades
托妮:不是.
Toni: No.
迈克:好的,那上面说什么呢?
Mike: Ok, what does that say?
托妮:它说……不,你来读出我的心思!
Toni: It says...No way, you read my mind!
迈克:好的,我也可以读出你的想法.你很难为情.
Mike: Yeah. And I can read your thought too. Shame on you.
托妮:我是难为情.
Toni: Shame on you.
迈克:朱莉!
Mike: Julie!
朱莉:不用管我.
Julie: Don't mind me.
托妮:迈克,这女人是谁?她干嘛拿着你的短裤?
Toni: Mike, who is this woman, and what's she doing with your shorts?
迈克:啊,她是个保姆,一个完美的女人.
Mike: Ah, she's an employee. That will be all my good woman.
朱莉:迈克,过奖了.
Julie: Mike, a word.
迈克:你给他们付工钱,他们就会把你当主人.
Mike: Later. You know you pay someone a salary and they think they own you.
朱莉:迈克,你要知道,你的房间不允许让女孩子进去.
Julie: Mike, you know you are not allowed to have girls in your room.
托妮:你是什么人,宝贝?
Toni: What are you, babe.
朱莉:你妈一回来,就可以吃晚饭了.
Julie: Dinner's on as soon as your mother gets home.
托妮:妈妈?
Toni: Mother?
迈克:啊,听着,托妮,我们刚才说到哪了?
Mike: Ah, listen. Toni, where were we?
托妮:迈克,我很抱歉,但我必须得走了.
Toni: Mike, I'm very sorry but I've got to leave.
迈克:嘿,不,
Mike: Hey, no, no, no, no, Toni. Come on. Don't listen to Julie.
不,托妮.跟我来,
I mean she's just someone that my parents hired to take care of my stupid
别听朱莉的,我是说她只是我父母雇来照顾我的小妹妹.
little sister.
托妮:不,我只是不想和不允许女孩子进入他们房间的人约会,
Toni: No, see. I just don't date guys who aren't allowed to have girls
我可不想坏我的名声.
in their rooms. I have a reputation.
迈克:托妮,托妮,托妮.
Mike: Toni, Toni, Toni. Come on. You just can't do this.
跟我进来,你不能这样做.到我的房间里来,
Walking into my room. Turn off the lights.
关上灯,开始说些调情的话,然后就走?
Start talking suggestive, and then just leave?
托妮:迈克,我无话可说,但我不是傻瓜.
Toni: Mike, I'm dumb, but I'm not stupid.
迈克:嘿,
Mike: Hey look Julie.
朱莉,到底是谁允许你随随便便走进我的房间,
Who the heck gave you permission to come barging up to my place any time
谁给了你钥匙?
you want. And who the heck gave you a key?
朱莉:是你,就在你说了"朱莉,
Julie: You did, right after you said "Julie,
随时欢迎你来我的房间"之后.
come up to my place any time you want".
迈克:好吧,我收回我的承诺,你把钥匙还给我.
Mike: Look, I withdraw that permission and you give me back my key.
你得知道,你没有权力进入我的,我的……
You know, you have no right to come barging into my, my uh...
朱莉:你的什么?
Julie: Into your what?
迈克:我的什么,什么.
Mike: Into my what what.
朱莉:是你一个人在说.
Julie: You're the one talking.
迈克:是的,很好.我以后会很感激的,如果你能保留你的……
Mike: Yeah, well, well look. I'd appreciate it in the future if you'd keep your...
朱莉:我的什么?
Julie: My what?
迈克:你的什么什么.嗯,如果你不打断我的话,也许我能够说完.
Mike: Your what what. Uh. Maybe I could finish if you'd stop interrupting me.
朱莉:我一个字也没说.迈克,我只是在做我的工作.
Julie: I haven't said a word. Look Mike. I'm just trying to do my job.
迈克:很好.提到你的工作,朱莉,你什么时候离开这儿?
Mike: Well uh. Speaking of your job Julie, what time do you get out of here?
朱莉:很快了.怎么了?
Julie: Pretty soon. Why?
迈克:好的,我想我马上就能行了,
Mike: Well, I bet I could make that right now.
我有了一些……哦,妈妈!
See I got a bit of pull with your...Uh mum!
朱莉:妈妈!
Julie: My mum!
麦琪:嘿,你们好.
Maggie: Hey gang.
朱莉:嘿,麦琪.晚饭在炉子上.
Julie: Hey Maggie. Dinner's on the stove.
麦琪:好,很好.你处理得很好,我……哦,
Maggie: Oh great. Were you able to arrange that thing that I...Oh Mike.
迈克,你去通知所有人,晚饭已经好了.
Could you go tell everybody that the dinner's ready?
迈克:好的,当然可以.
Mike: Yeah. Sure.
麦琪:现在就去.
Maggie: Now.
迈克:哦,好的,我一个一个去喊
Mike: Oh yeah. Don't anybody go anyplace.
麦琪:你能和我们一起去旅行吗?
Maggie: So you can make the trip with us?
朱莉:可以,我很乐意.
Julie: Yeah, it's fine.
麦琪:哦,很好,
Maggie: Oh great. I can't wait to tell the family, all at once as a surprise.
我要马上告诉全家,让他们大吃一惊.我这样做不会影响你们的周末安排吧?
Now I'm not ruining any weekend plans that you had am I?
朱莉:我有个约会,不过那不要紧,我可以换个时间.
Julie: Well, I had a date, but its no big deal. I can change it.
麦琪:朱莉.
Maggie: Julie.
朱莉:麦琪,相信我.
Julie: Maggie, believe me. Things weren't going anywhere with this guy.
我和这小伙子不会有什么结果,他没通过我的小威利测试.
He already failed my little Willie test.
麦琪:什么?
Maggie: Pardon me?
朱莉:哦,威利是我的小弟弟,
Julie: Oh, well Willie's my little baby brother.
我带他们去我父母家看威利,如果他们开始感到不安,
See I bring guys to my parents house to meet Willie,
说"嘿嘿,
and if they start getting real uncomfortable and saying " hey, hey, hey.
你弄脏了我的衣服",那么我就知道他只会浪费我的时间,
You're messing with my suit", then I know he's a waste of my time.
但是如果他开始逗他们玩,那么我就知道我已经找到了……
But if he starts playing around with them and stuff, then I know I've got a...
麦琪:一个看护人.
Maggie: A keeper.
朱莉:确实是.相当傻吧?
Julie: Exactly. Pretty nuts hu?
麦琪:不,相当聪明,
Maggie: No, it's pretty smart.
事实上,
In fact, could you mention that to Carol,
你可以告诉开萝尔,不过别让她听起来像是我让你说的.
and not make it sound like I said "can you mention that to Carol".
朱莉:可以,现在克莉丝在楼上睡觉,
Julie: Sure. Now Chrissy's upstairs sleeping.
我要回家收拾东西,一个小时后回来.
I'm going to go home and pack and be back in an hour.
麦琪:太好了,到时候见.
Maggie: Great. See you then.
朱莉:好的.
Julie: Ok.
迈克:朱莉离开了?
Mike: Did Julie leave?
麦琪:是的.
Maggie: Uh hu.
迈克:她去了哪?
Mike: Where did she go?
麦琪:事实上她……
Maggie: Well as a matter of fact she...
杰森:你好.
Jason: Hi.
麦琪:哦,你们好.坐下来,我有个好消息.
Maggie: Oh Hi everybody. Sit down, I have wonderful news.
本:是的,迈克已经告诉我们了,晚饭好了.
Ben: Yeah, like Mike already told us. Dinner's on.
麦琪:不,比那个更好.
Maggie: No. It's even better than that.
我们一直在谈论一起外出度周末,
You know how we've been talking about doing a getaway family weekend?
今晚出去怎么样,在玛莎葡萄园过两天?
Well how does leaving tonight, for two days in Martha's vineyard sound?
杰森:宝贝,你知道租间海滩别墅要多少钱吗?
Jason: Honey, you know how much those beech houses cost to rent?
开萝尔:在你们出去开心时,我只能看着克莉丝.
Carol: So I get stuck watching Chrissy, while you guys have a great time.
迈克:给我一张牌.
Mike: Drop me a card.
麦琪:杰森,第一,
Maggie: First of all Jason, my boss is letting us use his beach house,
我的老板让我使用他的海滩别墅,不用花钱.
free of charge.
杰森:免费!很好,很好.嘿,这听起来太好了,是吗,孩子们?
Jason: Free! Well, well, well, well. Hey, this sounds like fun, hey kids?
麦琪:第二朱莉刚才告诉我,她可以和我们一起去,帮助照看克莉丝.
Maggie: Julie just told me that she can come with us and help out with Chrissy.
开萝尔:哦,太好了,我去.
Carol: Oh great. I'm in.
麦琪:还有迈克.如果你对家庭周末不感兴趣的话,我不会……
Maggie: And Mike. Well, if you're not interested in a family weekend I don't...
迈克:妈妈,妈妈,我就盼着家庭欢聚,算上我.
Mike: Mum, mum. I live for family fun. Count me in.
杰森:说实话朱莉要来和你决定去没有什么关系吧?
Jason: So the fact that Julie's coming has nothing to do with your decision
to go?
迈克:朱莉去?
Mike: Julie going?
朱莉:嘘!克莉丝刚睡着,
Julie: Shhh! She just fell asleep.
杰森,如果我们现在离开,我想她会睡上一路的.
Jason, if we leave now I think she'll sleep the whole way.
杰森:我去看看麦琪准备好了没有.
Jason: Let me see if Maggie's ready.
朱莉:好的.
Julie: Ok.
迈克:爸爸,听着,我准备好了.反正我们要开两部车,我来带克莉丝吧?
Mike: Dad, listen, I'm ready now, and we got to take two cars anyway, so why don't I just take Chrissy.
杰森:当然可以,这是地址,你可以带上地图,以防万一.
Jason: Ok. Sure. Here's the address, and uh, why don't you take this map. Just incase.
迈克:我会迷路!爸爸,爸爸,爸爸.
Mike: Me get lost! Dad, dad, dad.
杰森:迈克,别逞能了,你还是带上地图吧?
Jason: Mike, cut the macho stuff. Would you just take the map please?
迈克:不,爸爸,我认为我应该把它留给你.
Mike: Well no dad, I thought that maybe I should leave it for you.
杰森:我会迷路!迈克,迈克,迈克,迈克.
Jason: Me get lost. Mike, Mike, Mike, Mike.
朱莉:我拿着.
Julie: Take it.
麦琪:本和开萝尔还在收拾.
Maggie: Ben and Carol are still packing.
杰森:好的,迈克和朱莉现在要去探路,这样克莉丝可以睡一会.
Jason: OK. Mike and Julie are going to hit the road now so Chrissy can get some sleep.
麦琪:但是我想让孩子跟着我们.
Maggie: But I wanted the baby with us.
杰森:麦琪,让这个熟睡的孩子好好躺着.
Jason: Maggie, lets let sleeping babies lie.
麦琪:可以了.
Maggie: Enough said.
麦琪:杰森,怎么四小时的路程花了五小时?
Maggie: Jason, why is a four hour ride taking five hours?
杰森:没花五小时.
Jason: It does not take five hours.
麦琪:算我不对,四小时五十八分,你答应说如果你找不到路的话,你会看地图.
Maggie: Excuse me, four hours and fifty eight minutes. You promised if you couldn't find the cut off, you'd look at the map.
杰森:好的,我没有.
Jason: Well, I didn't mmnmmm.
麦琪:什么?
Maggie: What?
杰森:我没拿地图.
Jason: I didn't bring the map.
开萝尔:他在开玩笑吧,妈妈?
Carol: He's kidding isn't he mum?
杰森:开萝尔,我看起来是开玩笑的语气吗?
Jason: Carol, do I seem to be in a jocular mood to you?
麦琪:都是男人的自以为是.
Maggie: Of all the silly macho things to do.
杰森:麦琪,我们会平安到达的,我有预感……
Jason: Maggie, we're going to be just fine. I have a feeling...
杰森和本:我们会不知不觉到的.
Jason and Ben: We'll be there before we know it.
杰森:我们应该把你留在斯汀奇家过周末.
Jason: Yeah, we could have left you at Stinky's for the weekend.
麦琪:只要你能带上那见鬼的地图,
Maggie: All of this could have been avoided if you just brought the stupid
所有的事情都可以避免.
map.
杰森:麦琪,如果我们带上地图,
Jason: Maggie, it wouldn't have made any difference if we brought the map.
也不会有什么不同.我是说很明显他们移动了标志,这个上面写着……
I mean obviously they've moved the sing for the cut off,The one that reads...
本:通往渡口.
Ben: To the ferry boat landing.
杰森:你看,本记得.
Jason: See even Ben remembers.
本:我当然记得,我们刚刚经过.
Ben: Of course I remember. We just passed it.
开萝尔:要在这买船票去玛莎葡萄园吗?
Carol: Is this where you buy the ferry tickets to Martha's Vineyard?
杰森:你应该说"是的".
Jason: You could have just "yes it is".
本:我们现在能上船吗?
Ben: Can we get on the boat now?
售票员:上学的孩子,你们为什么要上呢,它要到早上才开呢.
Ticket man: Course son. Don't see why you'd want to. It doesn't pull out till the morning.
麦琪:什么?
Maggie: What?
杰森:有其他办法去那个岛吗?
Jason: There's no other way to get on the island?
售票员:只能离开,除非你是条鱼,
Ticket man: Or off the island for that matter.
直接游过去.开个本地玩笑.
Unless you've got fins and a blow hole. Local joke.
杰森:我有个十来岁的儿子,
Jason: I got a teenage son and he's trapped on that island with a nineteen
和一个19岁的金发女郎被困在岛上了.
year old blond.
售票员:哦.他会怎么样呢?很好,我们到了,
Ticket man: Oh. What will become of him? Well, here we are.
客厅,卧室,和抽水马桶,太令人兴奋了.
A living room, bedroom and indoor plumbing. With a flusher.
朱莉:我把克莉丝放到楼上去.
Julie: I'll get Chrissy settled upstairs.
迈克:对不起,不过你看起来很面熟.
Mike: I'm sorry, but you look so familiar.
男人:也许你遇到了我的孪生兄弟,切斯特,
Man: Maybe you met my twin brother. Chester.
从陆地上渡船的时候,
Runs the ferry from the mainland. I got the looks and the personality.
相貌和个性都相似,只不过他负责渡船.
He got the ferry.
迈克:好的,我的家人要乘下一班,什么时候能到这儿?
Mike: Right, well my family is going to be coming up on the next ferry, so when does that get here?
男人:明天.
Man: Tomorrow.
迈克:什么?
Mike: Pardon me?
男人:只有早上才会有船抵达小岛,要不然就离开,除非你是条鱼,
Man: There's no way on or off this island till morning.
直接游过去,哈哈,本地玩笑.
Unless you've got fins and a blow hole. Ha ha ha. Local joke.
朱莉:我们只能整晚单独待在这儿吗?
Julie: So we are stuck here all night, alone?
男人:小姐,你和你的丈夫……
Man: Little lady. You and you're hubby....
朱莉:他不是我的丈夫.
Julie: He is not my husband.
男人:很好,对我来说一样,
Man: Well, makes no difference to me. I'm a liberal thinker.
我的思想很解放,不要像我弟弟那样假正经.晚安.
Not a prude like my brother. Good night.
朱莉:克莉丝已经安顿好了.
Julie: Chrissy's all settles up there.
迈克:很好,朱莉,看起来今晚就是你和我.
Mike: Well Julie, looks like it's just you and me tonight.
朱莉:你,我,还有克莉丝.
Julie: You, me and Chrissy.
迈克:哦,对.你,我还有克莉丝.
Mike: Oh right. You me and Chrissy. Oh what will they think of next.
哦,接下去他们会怎么想,这些睡袋挤在一起.
These sleeping bags zip together.
朱莉:迈克,我得对你说些事.
Julie: Mike, I've got to tell you something.
迈克:好的.
Mike: Yes.
朱莉:不太好说.
Julie: And this isn't easy.
迈克:来,朱莉.你说吧,什么都可以.
Mike: Oh come on Julie. You can tell me, you can tell me anything.
朱莉:今晚别碰我.
Julie: Don't hit on me tonight.
迈克:几乎是什么也不行.
Mike: Almost anything.
朱莉:我真的想说的好听些,但是……
Julie: I really didn't mean that the way that it sounded, but...
迈克:朱莉,朱莉,
Mike: Julie, Julie, its fine. Its fine, uh, in fact I am very relieved.
没事,没事,
I was thinking how am I going to fight this poor girl off,
事实上我倒放心了,我还在想我如何面对一个很想要我的可怜女孩.
who so obviously wants all of me.
(电话铃声)
(phone rings)
迈克:嗯,不碰.你好.
Mike: Uh hu hu. No touching. Hello.
杰森:迈克,是我.
Jason: Mike, it's me.
迈克:嘿,你们到底怎么回事?
Mike: Hey, what the heck happened to you guys?
杰森:我们错过了最后一班船,
Jason: Well, we missed the last ferry,
我们现在在"观鲸旅馆",我们很幸运,
so we are here at the quote "Historic Whale Watch Inn".
要了一个"那里她来"套间.
We are lucky enough to get the "there she blows" suite.
迈克:哦,你们现在好吧?
Mike: So, uh, are you guys doing ok?
本:还得再等会,开萝尔.
Ben: Its going to be a while Carol.
那个从俄亥俄来的胖子还占着浴室呢.
The fat guy from Ohio's still hogging the bathroom.
杰森:没法再好了.你怎么样?
Jason: Never better. So how about you?
迈克:这儿一切都很好.
Mike: Yeah, things are looking good here.
杰森:迈克,朱莉来这儿是照看克莉丝的.
Jason: Mike look. Just remember that Julie's there to look after Chrissy.
懂吗?我不想,
Ok. And I do not, and I repeat,
我再说一遍,不想让你认为你是和一个漂亮女孩整晚困在小岛上.
do not want you to think of her as a pretty girl you're stranded with
行吧?你要把朱莉当成,
all night on an island. Alright?
嗯,当成你的妈妈.
You got to think of Julie as, uh, as your mother.
迈克:爸爸,这太恶心了.
Mike: Dad, that's sick.
本:快点,我登不了了.
Ben: Come on, I'm dying out here.
杰森:本,告诉你妈妈,我在和迈克通电话.
Jason: Ben, tell your mother I've got mike on the phone.
本:我不能,我不想失去位置,
Ben: I can't. I don't want to lose my shot if the fat guy gives up
要是那个胖子洗完的话.
the can.
杰森:我喊她,迈克,你别挂电话.
Jason: I'll get her. Mike, hold on will you.
本:你这只狡猾的狗.
Ben: You sly dog.
迈克:嘿,你在说什么?
Mike: Hey, what are you talking about?
本:哦,听我说,
Ben: Oh come on,
你向渡船的家伙行贿,让他取消了最后一班船,
you bribed that ferry boat guy to cancel the last boat so you could make
这样你就可以和朱莉亲近了,是吧?
moves on Julie. Didn't you?
迈克:嗯,现在可真冷,不过我希望很快暖和起来.
Mike: Well, uh. It is a bit chilly now, but I am expecting a warm front soon.
本:妈妈来了,祝你睡个好觉.
Ben: Here's mum. Sleep well.
麦琪:你好,迈克,我的小宝宝怎么样?
Maggie: Hi Mike. How's my baby?
迈克:妈妈,我很好.
Mike: Please mum. I'm fine.
麦琪:我是说克莉丝.
Maggie: I meant Chrissy.
迈克:哦哦,她也很好.
Mike: Oh, oh, she's fine too.
开萝尔:啊!
Carol: Ahh!
本:你不是来自俄亥俄的胖子.
Ben: You're not the fat guy from Ohio.
开萝尔:嗯!
Carol: Hu!
本:嘿.
Ben: Hey.
麦琪:迈克,我希望你今晚做个绅士.
Maggie: Mike, I hope you are going to be a gentleman tonight.
迈克:妈妈,我什么时候不是个绅士呢?
Mike: Mum, when have I not been a gentleman?
麦琪:哈哈哈.太好笑了.听着,我只希望你把朱莉当成……
Maggie: Ha ha ha. That's funny. Listen, I just want you to think of Julie as, well,
迈克:你?
Mike: You?
麦琪:迈克.这太恶心了.但是你明白了就好,我要和朱莉说.
Maggie: Mike, that's sick. But you get the idea. Ok, let me talk to Julie.
迈克:好的,嘿,朱莉,我妈妈.
Mike: Ok. Hey Julie, it's my mum.
朱莉:你好.
Julie: Hi.
麦琪:你好,朱莉.我的小宝宝好吗?
Maggie: Hi Julie. Is my baby ok?
朱莉:我们已经约法三章,我相信他会表现得很好的.
Julie: Well now that we got the ground rules down, I think he'll be just fine.
麦琪:他?
Maggie: He?
朱莉:开个玩笑.克莉丝很好.
Julie: Just kidding. Chrissy is great.
麦琪:太好了.谢谢你,朱莉.再见.
Maggie: Great. Well thank you Julie. Bye bye.
朱莉:再见.
Julie: Bye bye.
杰森:宝贝,你看上去很担心.
Jason: Honey, you look worried.
麦琪:是的,因为这是我的宝宝第一次单独过夜.
Maggie: Well it's just that it's my baby's first night alone.
杰森:和一个女孩,我知道.
Jason: With a girl. I know.
麦琪和杰森:那倒也是.
Maggie and Jason: That too.
迈克:注意到有什么不同吗?
Mike: Notice anything different?
朱莉:你穿了件很搞笑的夹克.
Julie: You are wearing that silly smoking jacket.
迈克:观察很敏锐,尽管这不是我的.
Mike: Very observant. It's not mine though.
朱莉:我不这样认为.
Julie: I didn't think so.
迈克:好了,朱莉.挑一张牌,随便哪一张,我将猜出你的心思.好,你的牌是黑桃A吗?
Mike: Alright Julie. Pick a card, any card and I will read your mind. Ok, was your card the ace of spades?
朱莉:不是.
Julie: That's not it.
迈克:好,但是我问题的答案是……
Mike: Ok, but the answer to my question is...
朱莉:那是另一张牌.
Julie: It's another card.
迈克:答案是一个字……算了,我讨厌扑克把戏.朱莉,我,我真的尊重那些知书达理的女人.你知道,我不是那种只是把每一个女人当成玩物的男人.
Mike: So the one word answer is...Forget it. I hate card tricks. You know Juice. Um...I,I,I really tespect a woman who's into the book thing. You know,I'm not the type of man who thinks of every woman as a  mere play thing.
朱莉:应该是每一个其它的女人.
Julie: Just every other woman.
迈克:朱莉,你让我很惊讶.
Mike: Julie, I'm surprised at you.
你知道我的意思,
You know I mean, hey,
嘿,你看起来喜欢我亲近你.
you act like I'm trying to put a move on you or something.
朱莉:迈克,坦诚些.
Julie: Mike, just be honest.
迈克:坦诚?
Mike: Honest?
朱莉:是的,我喜欢坦诚.
Julie: Yeah, I like honest.
迈克:你喜欢坦诚?
Mike: You like honest?
朱莉:非常喜欢.
Julie: Very much.
迈克:好的,我给你坦诚,
Mike: Alright. I'll give you honest, I'll give you honest up the Wazoo.
我会对你坦诚到底.我是说,我认为你很可爱.
I mean, I think you are cute.
朱莉:你嘴真甜,迈克,我认为你也有点可爱.
Julie: That's sweet. Mike. I think you are kind of cute too.
迈克:真的?
Mike: Really? Yeah. Well I also think,
我也认为,只要坦诚能一直保持下去,
as long as this honesty deal is cooking,
我们就能成为可爱的一对.
that we could possibly make a cute couple.
朱莉:迈克,
Julie: Mike, it takes me more to get interested in a guy than being really
光靠很可爱是不能让我对一个男孩产生兴趣的.
cute.
迈克:哦,现在是很可爱.
Mike: Oh, so now it's really cute. A minute ago you said kinda cute.
一分钟以前你说有点,
It sounds to me like you are not being totally honest.
这听起来你没有完全坦诚,我们不能继续这次谈话了.
I can't continue this conversation.
朱莉:哦,迈克,我认为你很迷人.
Julie: Ok. Mike, I do think you are attractive.
迈克:我相信你说的是很迷人.
Mike: I believe you said really attractive.
朱莉:但是如果人们只寻找很迷人的人,
Julie: But if people just went for people that they found really attractive,
结果会怎样呢?
where would we be?
迈克:确切地说,我正在寻找一个丑女人.
Mike: Exactly. I'm holding out for an ugly woman.
朱莉:你是个很有趣的孩子.
Julie: You're a pretty funny kid.
迈克:孩子,嗯,那很有趣.你真的这么认为?
Mike: A kid. Hu. That's funny. You really meant that, didn't you?
朱莉:是的.
Julie: Well yeah.
迈克:无论如何,我是完全没有机会了.好的,
Mike: So I have absolutely no shot here, whatsoever? Oh fine.
很好,很好.我太傻了,
Fine, fine, fine. I was crazy to think that you'd think that I was...
以为你认为我是……你可能把我当成和本一样.是吗?
You probably think of me the same as you do Ben. Right? Yeah.
是的,我穿了一件很傻的夹克,所有一切都是这样.
And I wore a stupid smoking jacket and everything.
朱莉:迈克,迈克,
Julie: Mike. Mike, I didn't mean to insult you.
我不打算伤害你.也许我们还是不谈为好.
Maybe it's just better if we don't talk.
迈克:只是要说明一下,
Mike: So just to be totally clear,
我对你完全没有吸引力吗?
you have absolutely no attraction here what so ever?
朱莉:我没有这么说.
Julie: I didn't say that.
迈克:那么你承认,有一点点吸引力?
Mike: So you admit, there is some kind of attraction?
朱莉:你小的时候也总是这样吗?
Julie: Were you always like this as a child?
迈克:是的,差不多,可能要矮一些.你呢?我是说你是小孩子的时候你喜欢这样子吗?
Mike: Yeah. Pretty much. Maybe a little shorter. What about you? I mean, were you like this when you were a child?
朱莉:哦,不.当我是一个小女孩时,我相当保守.
Julie: Oh no. When I was a little girl, I was very uptight.
迈克:你也经变化很大了.
Mike: You've come a long way.
朱莉:我是变了.
Julie: Actually I have.
我要告诉你件事.我很害羞,
I'll tell you something,
直到十六岁才有了第一次约会.
I was so shy that I didn't have my first date until I was sixteen.
迈克:那不奇怪.
Mike: That's not so weird. I mean I didn't have my first date until I was...
我是说我的第一次约会直到……真的?
really?
朱莉:对于我来说,
Julie: It was hard for me to get to know any boys.
认识个男孩很难.
We moved around a lot.
我们经常搬家.我爸爸在海军陆战队,
See my dad was in the marines, and,
我差不多去过了世界上每一个不讲英语的地方.
gosh I've lived just about every place in the world where people don't
我可能在十六岁以前被邀请过,
even speak English. Maybe I did get asked out before I was sixteen.
但是我真的不知道他们在说什么.
But I really never knew what they were saying.
迈克:因此我决定报考阿尔夫兰登初级大学,看看结果如何?
Mike: So I decided to sign up to Alf Landen Junior college and see what happened.
朱莉:但是你是真想成为一名演员吗?
Julie: But you are serious about wanting to give acting a try?
迈克:是的,
Mike: Yeah, I think so.
我想是这样,
I mean it was the only part of high school I was any good at.
这是我高中时唯一擅长的.但是真正要做的想法让我害怕得要命,
But, uh, the thought of actually doing it scares me to death.
我不敢告诉任何人.
That's something I never told anybody.
朱莉:这种样子很纯净,就是聊天,
Julie: Isn't this kind of neat. Just talking.
像朋友,没有喜欢,你懂的.
Like friends, and not like, you know.
迈克:是的.谁知道呢?
Mike: Yeah, it is. Who knew?
嗯,我们刚才说到你在约会的那个男孩.
So, uh, we were talking about the guys you were dating.
朱莉:什么时候说了?
Julie: When were we doing that?
迈克:嘿,如果你不愿意说你和谁约会的话题,那么我们可以换个话题.
Mike: Hey look, if you are uncomfortable with the subject of who you are dating, then we can change the subject.
朱莉:好的.
Julie: Fine.
迈克:谁约了你?
Mike: So who's dating you?
朱莉:好,我一直和这个男孩约会.
Julie: Ok, I've been dating this guy.
迈克:真是这样?我坐得很认真吧?
Mike: There you go. I sit serious?
朱莉:没有.
Julie: No.
迈克:没有,他不可能像我一样对这次谈话这么感兴趣.
Mike: No, he's probably not into this talking thing like I am.
朱莉:那么你呢,进入你房间的那个女孩是你女朋友吗?
Julie: Well what about you. Was that girl in your apartment your girlfriend?
迈克:托妮?不是托妮.
Mike: Toni? Toni, no.
朱莉:为什么,她哪点不好呢?
Julie: Why, is there something wrong with her?
迈克:不,她没有什么不好,
Mike: No, there's nothing wrong with her, it's just that...
那只是……我不知道,如果我要有一个女朋友,她得……有更多.
I don't know, if I'm going to have a girlfriend,she's got to have...more.
朱莉:在我看来,托妮有很多.
Julie: Toni looked like she had plenty to me.
迈克:不,我不是指更多那个,我是指……
Mike: No, I don't mean more like that. I mean...
朱莉:迈克,我喜欢你不知道要接下去说什么时的样子.
Julie: Mike, I like you when you don't know what to say next.
迈克:天哪,我不知道接下去说什么.
Mike: Well gosh. I don't know what to say next.
朱莉:你知道,迈克,我想我也正在寻找更多.
Julie: You know Mike, I guess I'm looking for more too.
迈克:是的.什么?
Mike: Yeah. What?
朱莉:很难用几个词来表达,但是我想当我找到时,
Julie: Well, it's hard to put into words but I think I'll know him when
我会知道的.
I find him.
迈克:是的,我想我知道你的意思.
Mike: Yeah, I think I know what you mean.
我以前和很多像托妮那样的女孩约会过,
I've dated a lot of girls like Toni before, but, I don't know,
但是,我不知道为什么,
lately it's getting tough.
最近变得很糟糕.就像上个星期,
I mean, it's like last week,
我和这个相当热火的女孩在开车兜风中,
I went out with this incredibly hot babe at this drive in and I fell asleep.
我却睡着了.可不要把我告诉你的告诉其他人.
Please don't ever tell anybody that I told you that.
(婴儿哭泣声)
(baby's crying)
迈克:朱莉!好了,我来了,克莉丝.嘿,如果你不哭了,我把我的车给你.怎么样,克莉丝?嘿,我想你会喜欢我的车.有五档,开起来很好.你想要拨浪鼓吗?你过来,过来.嘿,过来.嘿,嘿,嘿,我们都是猴子,人们说我们是猴子,我要一直唱,因为你现在笑了.嘿,你是个小孩子,哒嘀哒嘀哒哒哒……哦,你在这儿多久了?
Mike: Julie! Alright, I'm coming Chrissy. I'm coming. Hey look, if you stop crying, I'll give you my car. How you doing Chrissy, hu? Hey,I think you'll like my car. It's a five speed.Driving stick. Good. You want your rattle? Here you go, Here you  go. Hey come on. Hey hey hey. Hey hey we're the monkeys, people say we monkey around, I will keep on singing,because you're smiling now. Hey hey you're a baby,doo dee doo dee dii doo doo...Uh, hi.How long have you been, uh?
朱莉:昨天我和你妈妈说我的小威利测试的时候,你在听,是吧?
Julie: You were listening when I was telling your mum about my little Willie test yesterday.weren't you?
迈克:哦?
Mike: Hu?
朱莉:不,你不可能.
Julie: No, you couldn't have been.
迈克:嗯,朱莉.你为什么这样看着我?
Mike: Uh, Julie. Why are you looking at me like that?
朱莉:你不是我想的那种人.
Julie: Cos you are not who I thought you were.
迈克:是的.我是怎样的?
Mike: Yeah. Well who am I?
朱莉:你更多.
Julie: You are more.
迈克:哦,不,不不.你想让我开始以为,我又有了一次机会,然后你再对我说不.是吗?
Mike: Oh no. No no no no no. You're going to make me start thinking that I've got a shot again, and then you're going to tell em no. Right?
朱莉:不是.
Julie: No.
迈克:是否定,还是肯定?
Mike: Well then, a no no, or a no yes?
朱莉:肯定.
Julie: Yes.
迈克:是肯定?
Mike: Yes yes?
朱莉:不说了,迈克.(亲一下)这不可能发生,我替你父母干活.
Julie: Shut up Mike. (kiss) This can't happen. I work for your parents.
迈克:哦,哦!听好了,这个周末你不必工作,对吧?
Mike: Oh, oh! Well listen. You don't work on the weekends, do you?
朱莉:但是我比你大,在你一岁时,我有你两倍大.
Julie: But I'm older than you and when you were one I was twice as old as you.
迈克:啊,是,但是当你十岁时,我九岁,你只比我大十分之一.
Mike: Ah, yeah, but when you were ten, and I nine, you were only ten percent older than me.
朱莉:是的,但是
Julie: Yeah, but...
迈克:现在你是十九岁,我是十八岁,你只比我……很好,关键在于,
Mike: And now that you are nineteen and I'm eighteen, that makes you only....
我一直在追赶你.按这样的速度,我会追上你甚至反超的.
Well the point is,I'm gaining on you.This way,I could maybe even pass you.
朱莉:但是,别超过我,迈克.
Julie: But, don't pass me Mike.
迈克:也许只是赶上.
Mike: Maybe just catch up.
朱莉:克莉丝要换尿布了.
Julie: Chrissy needs changing.
迈克:是的.
Mike: Yeah.
迈克:嘿,朱莉……
Mike: Hey Julie...
朱莉:嗯?
Julie: Uh hu?
迈克:今晚和你一起度过,真愉快.
Mike: It was nice spending the night with you.
朱莉:迈克?西维尔,你真得很绅士.
Julie: Michael Seaver, you really are neat.
迈克:我很绅士.嘿,嘿.妈妈,爸爸,你们怎么样?
Mike: I'm neat. Hey hey. Mumo, dadio. How's it going?
麦琪:你好,迈克.克莉丝在哪?
Maggie: Hi Mike. Where's Chrissy?
迈克:她和朱莉在一起,嘿,爸爸.
Mike: Uh, she's up in the room with Julie. Hey dad.
杰森:迈克,你睡得好吗?
Jason: So mike. Did you sleep well?
迈克:几乎没睡.我是说,嗯……看,爸爸,
Mike: Hardly at all. I mean, uh...Look dad. Dad.
爸爸.你担心的事没有发生,所以你不需要担心了.
Nothing you are worried about happened, so you don't need to worry bout it.
开萝尔:本,我一个人拿不动.
Carol: Ben, I can't carry this all by myself.
本:那就找人帮忙呗.
Ben: Then get some help.
迈克:我要去帮他们卸东西.
Mike: I'm going to go help the kids unload the car.
杰森:嘿,迈克,你出于什么考虑?
Jason: Hey mike. What's your angle?
迈克:没有考虑.
Mike: No angle.
杰森:麦琪,迈克说他和朱莉之间什么也没发生,我很困惑.
Jason: Maggie, Mike says nothing happened between him and Julie and I'm very confused
麦琪:为什么?
Maggie: Why.
杰森:我相信他.
Jason: Cos I believe him.
麦琪:杰森,我没看见他们在一起,他们没什么相似点.
Maggie: Jason, I don't see them together. They don't have much in common.
杰森:按照弗洛伊德理论,我看到了诱惑,
Jason: Well I can see the attraction in Freudian terms.
你知道男人通常会勾引看起来像他们妈妈的女人.
You know men are often attracted to women who remind them of their mothers.
麦琪:哦,你认为朱莉让他想起了我?杰森:是的.她金发碧眼,
Maggie: Oh, you think Julie reminds him of me? Jason: Yeah. Sure.
聪明可爱,而且不够理性……呵呵.00:22:46,100
She's blond, she's smart. She's cute. Not much of a sense of hu...Hu li li.